totalbankruptcy.com 2007-12-10

# Total Bankruptcy Privacy Policy on Your Personal Information

## Privacy Policy 

### Last Updated: April 2007 

All of the information we obtain about you is stored securely on our website, and we use it only to evaluate your situation and provide the services described in our Terms and Conditions to you, to allow unaffiliated sponsoring lawyers or law firms to evaluate your case and provide legal services to you, to provide ongoing communications to you in furtherance of these legal services, and as set forth below. Except as set forth below, we do not sell or share your personal information with anyone other than our own internal personnel and the unaffiliated sponsoring lawyers and law firms, and certain authorized third parties (such as expert witnesses) who may be retained to assist in your bankruptcy case. As part of this process, those third parties agree to keep your information confidential and agree not to share it with any third party without your express permission. 

Note that we may contact you directly from time to time with offers and/or promotions which we believe may be of interest to you. You are free to opt-out of receiving these communications at any time by sending an e-mail to [privacy@TotalBankruptcy.com](mailto:privacy@TotalBankruptcy.com) with “ **Please remove me from Total Attorneys Marketing List** ” in the subject line, or by checking the appropriate box below and filling in your email address. 

Please also note that we may, from time to time, “lease” or “rent” lists to third party marketers (and/or brokers who work with such third party marketers) which contain your personal information to allow such marketers to contact the individuals included on the list with offers and/or information which they believe may be of interest to you and such other individuals. We make no representations or warranties whatsoever regarding these marketers and/or the products or services they are offering. Please note that you may have your name removed from any such lists by either sending an e-mail to [privacy@TotalBankruptcy.com](mailto:privacy@TotalBankruptcy.com) with **“Please remove me from all Partner Marketing Lists”** in the subject line, or by checking the appropriate box below and filling in your email address. 

**Please remove me from:**

TotalAttorneys Marketing Lists Partner Marketing Lists 

### What types of information about you do we collect through this website? 

We collect personal information about you (and certain of your family members) in three principal ways: (1) information you provide us through this website; (2) information that is automatically generated when you use our website; and (3) information we obtain from third parties. 

With respect to information you provide us on this website, we collect the following information from you: 

  * Your name, residence and email addresses, and telephone numbers
  * Similar information for your spouse and/or dependents
  * Information regarding your assets, debts, income, and expenses

We also collect certain information about you automatically when you visit our website. Through our use of "cookies" (cookies are electronic identifiers that are transferred automatically to your computer through your browser and they allow our computers to save certain information you provide us and store information about you so we can recognize you when you visit our website in the future). Other types of information we collect automatically include your Internet Protocol (IP) address (which allows us to understand how you use our site and to enable us to make changes to our site in order to improve your user experience); information regarding your computer and your connection to our site (such as your browser type, operating system, and platform); and your user history to, through, and away from our site, including your session information, page loading times, page errors and broken links, the length of your visits to specific pages within our site, and other information related to your experience on our site. 

From time to time, we collect information about you from third parties, such as updated contact information, and search term and search result information from your web searches. 

All of the information we obtain about you is stored securely on our website, and we use it only to evaluate your situation and provide legal services to you, to allow unaffiliated sponsoring lawyers or law firms to evaluate your case and provide legal services to you, and to provide ongoing communications to you in furtherance of these legal services. Except as set forth elsewhere in this policy, we do not sell or share your personal information with anyone other than our own internal personnel and the unaffiliated sponsoring lawyers and law firms, and certain authorized third parties (such as expert witnesses) who may be retained to assist in your bankruptcy case. As part of this process, those third parties agree to keep your information confidential and agree not to share it with any third party without your express permission. 

We only disclose any personally identifiable information about individual users in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, or when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with applicable laws, valid legal process, a court order, a current judicial proceeding, or to protect our rights or property. 

We disclose personally identifiable individual information and the other information you provide us to unaffiliated sponsoring lawyers or law firms in order for them to contact you and to determine whether to handle your case. As part of this process, those lawyers or law firm agrees to keep your information confidential and agree not to share it with any third party without your express permission. 

We may also provide aggregate statistical information (such as the city or state you live in) to third parties to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. We will not, however, disclose any personally identifiable information about to these parties. 

**How do you protect my personal information?  
**Please understand that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (such as through an email message or through filling out an online form), this information cannot be made 100 percent secure and, in some cases, that information can be intercepted, collected and used by others. However, we work hard to protect your information at all times, and we protect you information in several ways. We store your information on a secure server that only TotalBankruptcy.com and its authorized personnel can access through a password. Additionally, we encrypt your information to prevent third parties without authorization from intercepting your information when it is in transit to us. 

### Questions about our Privacy Policy? 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us at: 

#### TotalBankruptcy

Attn: Edmund Scanlan

   25 East Washington, Suite 510  
Chicago, IL 60602

   (312) 252-1313  

You can also review and update the personal information we have about you in order to ensure its accuracy. To do so, please contact us at the above address. 

### Updates to Privacy Statement 

From time to time, we may decide to change the provisions of this privacy policy, and we reserve the right to do so, without notice. However, we will attempt to inform you of any changes to this policy, whether by email alerts, changes to our website and/or through personal communications with you. 

### Links 

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website
